getpeek.com 2010-12-31

# Peek 9. Connect everyone, everywhere.

Any personally identifying information submitted on the Peek Web site is subject to our Privacy Policy, available at http://www.getpeek.com/privacy.htm, the terms of which are incorporated herein. Please review our Privacy Policy to understand our practices. The date of any changes to our Privacy Policy will be noted at the bottom of our Privacy Policy.

The security of your information is important to us at Peek. We use a number of physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect your email and payment information from unauthorized access. These include, for example, using the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol and encryption technologies to protect your data, and policies limiting access to systems that store personal information to authorized personnel. Wireless systems use radios to transmit communications over a complex network. We do not guarantee that your communications using the Service will be private or secure, and we are not liable to you for any lack of privacy or security you may experience.

You are responsible for taking precautions and providing security measures best suited for your situation and intended use of the Service. You should keep your email login and password safe and confidential to protect against unauthorized access to your information. Use passwords that others may not guess easily. Do not give your passwords to anyone else unless you intend that they have the same ability to access your information that you do. If you write down your passwords or user names, keep them in a safe location.

We strive to protect the information we have about you. Our internal policies limit access to personally identifiable information to employees, agents, affiliates, supplies, vendors, consultants, and contractors who need it to serve you. Peek employees are contractually obligated to protect your information, and we work to ensure that our employees do not tamper with or intentionally disclose the contents of any communication. We use physical security measures and passwords and other access control mechanisms to protect our data systems from unauthorized access.

If required by law or to protect our rights, business, network, or customers, we may (but are not required to) monitor, intercept, and disclose your transmissions, location, or communications and may disclose your billing, account, or other information, in good faith reliance on legal process. The way third-parties handle and use your personal information is governed by their policies, and we are not responsible for their policies or their compliance with them.

(Revised August 22, 2008)
